[

{
    "quiz_id":0,
    "question_category":"common",
   "question": "Which one is correct team name in NBA?",
    "options": [
        "New York Bulls",
        "Los Angeles Kings",
        "Golden State Warriros",
        "Huston Rocket"
    ],
    "answer": 4
}, {
    "quiz_id":0,
    "question_category":"common",
    "question": "5 + 7 = ?",
    "options": [
        "10",
        "11",
        "12",
        "13"
    ],
    "answer": 3
},
{

   "quiz_id":0,
   "question_category":"common",
   "question": "12 - 8 = ?",
   "options": [
       "1",
       "2",
       "3",
       "4"
   ],
   "answer": 4
},

{
    "quiz_id":0,
    "question_category":"common",
   "question": "Which one is correct team name in NBA?",
    "options": [
        "New York Bulls",
        "Los Angeles Kings",
        "Golden State Warriros",
        "Huston Rocket"
    ],
    "answer": 4
}, {
    "quiz_id":0,
    "question_category":"common",
    "question": "5 + 7 = ?",
    "options": [
        "10",
        "11",
        "12",
        "13"
    ],
    "answer": 3
},
{

   "quiz_id":0,
   "question_category":"common",
   "question": "12 - 8 = ?",
   "options": [
       "1",
       "2",
       "3",
       "4"
   ],
   "answer": 4
},
{
    "quiz_id":0,
    "question_category":"common",
   "question": "Which one is correct team name in NBA?",
    "options": [
        "New York Bulls",
        "Los Angeles Kings",
        "Golden State Warriros",
        "Huston Rocket"
    ],
    "answer": 4
}, {
    "quiz_id":0,
    "question_category":"common",
    "question": "5 + 7 = ?",
    "options": [
        "10",
        "11",
        "12",
        "13"
    ],
    "answer": 3
},
{

   "quiz_id":0,
   "question_category":"common",
   "question": "12 - 8 = ?",
   "options": [
       "1",
       "2",
       "3",
       "4"
   ],
   "answer": 4
},
{

   "quiz_id":0,
   "question_category":"common",
   "question": "12 - 8 = ?",
   "options": [
       "1",
       "2",
       "3",
       "4"
   ],
   "answer": 4
}
]
